itwire.com 2009-12-16

# iTWire - PRIVACY

ITWire Pty.Ltd (ACN 115579069 ), publishes ITWire, a website and associated daily newsletter, both of which incorporate TheBeerFiles and ExchangeAlert. ITWire has developed this statement in accordance with the National Privacy Principles to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy, integrity and ethical practices. This policy sets out how ITWire (www.iTWire.com.au) uses your personal information and explains, according to privacy laws. 

  * Disclosure
  * How ITWire uses the information we collect or which is provided by other parties 
  * What kind of personal information ITWire collects and how it is collected 
  * How ITWire treats sensitive information 
  * Updating personal information 
  * Accessing the personal information that ITWire holds about registered users of our site, newsletters or publications, including ITWire Update incorporating TheBeerFiles and ExchangeAlert 
  * Management and security of personal information 
  * How to contact The Beer Files 
  * Disclaimer 
  * Terms of Use

The ITWire website and online newsletter, ITWire Update, are wholly owned by ITWire Pty.Ltd.. ITWire carries information, news, views and opinions about people, companies and organisations in the Australian IT & T business sector and also carries advertisements for companies their products and services.

This policy applies only to The ITWire site (www.iTWire.com.au) and the ITWireUpdate newsletter. ITWire publishes this privacy statement as a demonstration of its commitment to ensuring the confidentiality and privacy of personal information supplied to us by subscribers. 

What Type of Information ITWire collects

When you register with ITWire you provide us with your name, email address, occupation and position. If you do register to receive ITWire emails or other information we might choose to send you from time to time, information about your interest may be collected and stored. This information is recorded on the servers of our webmaster and used by ITWire for purposes of targeting advertising, learning more about your interests and to allow us to keep you updated with the latest news and information. Readers of ITWire and users of the website have the option to opt out or deregister themselves and to discontinue any services we provide, including weekly update emails sent to the IP address provided by you.

How ITWire uses the information we collect and/or which is supplied to us

ITWire may use information it collects from you, as a registered visitor to the site, or as a registered reader of the ITWire Update newsletter, for the primary purpose for which it is collected and for other secondary purposes that are related to the primary purpose of collection. ITWire uses personal information to:  
∑ Help us gain an understanding of what type of readers are visiting our site, the work they do, their position within the company or organisation   
∑ Assist us in understanding what sections of the site or newsletter users are attracted to, the frequency of their visits and their usage of the site or newsletter   
∑ Allows us to respond directly to user interests and helps our advertisers understand the audience they are reaching  
We may also make use of registered users IP addresses to help analyse problems with our server, to administer our website and to gather broad demographic information. When visiting our website, a record of the user's visit is logged. Information supplied by the user's browser may include the server address, operating system, the date and time of the visit, pages accessed and the type of browser used. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable.

How ITWire deals with sensitive information

ITWire may use and disclose sensitive information only for the purpose for which it is provided or a directly related secondary purpose or as allowed by law unless you have agreed otherwise

Accessing & updating your information

You can use our website to correct/update your email address at any time. You can update the information provided by you to ITWire at any time when online by sending the new information to [editor@iTWire.com.au](mailto:editor@iTWire.com.au)

Management and security of personal information

ITWire does not share any of your personally identifiable information with any other person or entity

Disclosure

We may disclose your personal information to external service providers that provide services for the purposes of our business, on a confidential basis, for example, including but not limited to representatives of any agency or company we use to solicit advertising for the site, those companies or organisations that may choose to advertise with us, and our IT support providers. However, no party is ever allowed direct access to the registered users' personal information held by ITWire.  
Disclaimer  
This Disclaimer and Exclusion of Liability applies to ITWire Pty.Ltd (CAN 115579069), this web site, newsletters or and any other site or publication containing ITWire name. 

ITWire encourages any party viewing this web site or newsletter to exercise discretion while browsing the Internet. ITWire does not represent, warrant, or endorse the accuracy, reliability, copyright compliance, completeness or timeliness of any of the information, content, views, opinions, representations or advertisements contained on, distributed, linked, downloaded or accessed from any of the services contained on this web site or on ITWire newsletters. ITWire accepts no responsibility for the comments, views and opinions of others who may, from to time, have those comments, views and opinions carried on the ITWire site or in the ITWire Update newsletter.  
Your use of this Website is at your own risk. ITWire does not warrant that the site is free of viruses or other components that may infect, harm or cause damage to your computer equipment or any other property when you access, browse, download from or otherwise use this website. Under no circumstances, including but not limited to ITWire’s ' own negligence, shall ITWire be liable for any consequential, direct, incidental, indirect, or other special damages related to the use or the inability to use all errors or omissions in the contents and functioning of this website. ITWire and our website may contain links to sites and resources that are maintained by third parties. If you choose to visit these, please note that ITWire is not responsible for the privacy practices, content or availability of such sites or resources. ITWire does not endorse or is liable for any content, advertising, products, or other information, comment or opinions available from third-parties, their sites or resources. ITWire is not responsible, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the use or reliance on any such content or services available on these sites or resources, or in the comments and opinions of these third-parties.

TERMS OF USE

Your use of our internet site or daily newsletter, or any of the products or services offered on the site or newsletter (collectively the “services”) is subject to these Terms of Use (these “Terms”). We may modify these terms at any time without notice to you by posting revised Terms on our site. Your use of our site or newsletter constitutes your binding acceptance of these terms, including any modifications that we make.

We have the right, but not the obligation, to take any of the following actions in our sole discretion at any time and for any reason without giving you any prior notice:

1\. Restrict, suspend or terminate your access to all or any part of our Services;  
2\. Change, suspend or discontinue all or any part of our Services:  
3\. Refuse, move or remove any material that you submit to our site or newsletter for any reason;  
4\. Refuse, move or remove any content that is available on our site or newsletter  
5\. Deactivate or delete your account(s) and all related information and files in your account;  
6\. Establish general practices and limits concerning use of our sites

You agree that we will not be liable to you or any third party for taking any of these actions.

You understand and agree that our Services may include communications such as service announcements and administrative messages from us or from our partners and that these communications are considered part of the Services. You will not be able to opt out of receiving these messages. You also understand that our Services may include advertisements.

How to contact ITWire

You may contact ITWire by sending an email to [editor@iTWire.com.au](mailto:editor@iTWire.com.au) or [publisher@iTWire.com.au](mailto:publisher@iTWire.com.au) All advertising enquires should be directed to the Publisher at [advert@iTWire.com.au](mailto:advert@iTWire.com.au)

TERMS OF USE

Your use of our internet site or daily newsletter, or any of the products or services offered on the site or newsletter (collectively the “services”) is subject to these Terms of Use (these “Terms”). We may modify these terms at any time without notice to you by posting revised Terms on our site. Your use of our site or newsletter constitutes your binding acceptance of these terms, including any modifications that we make.

We have the right, but not the obligation, to take any of the following actions in our sole discretion at any time and for any reason without giving you any prior notice:

7\. Restrict, suspend or terminate your access to all or any part of our Services;  
8\. Change, suspend or discontinue all or any part of our Services:  
9\. Refuse, move or remove any material that you submit to our site or newsletter for any reason;  
10\. Refuse, move or remove any content that is available on our site or newsletter  
11\. Deactivate or delete your account(s) and all related information and files in your account;  
12\. Establish general practices and limits concerning use of our sites

You agree that we will not be liable to you or any third party for taking any of these actions.

You understand and agree that our Services may include communications such as service announcements and administrative messages from us or from our partners and that these communications are considered part of the Services. You will not be able to opt out of receiving these messages. You also understand that our Services may include advertisements.
